いや…
怒りになるのか？
それは喜びや
淀みの中で目を開けて
水面のさざ波に名前を付けるなら
この海は そんな言葉では浅すぎる
この深い水底に
何がいるのか知りたいなら
下へと 冷たくて重い水を
蹴り続けるしかない
人の心を海とするならば
きっとその水は淀んでいる
自分という人間を知りたいなら
たとえ 底が無かろうと
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかしVIPなエア・フォース
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの どうして？
知らない間に
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
If you compared a person’s heart to the sea,
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
then the water would surely be stagnant.
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
If I were to describe the waves that disturb the surface,
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
then they would be joy, or even anger.
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
No.
These words are too shallow for the sea.
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
To know what’s in the depth of the sea,
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
open your eyes in the stagnation
and keep kicking toward the cold sea’s bottom.
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
That is, if you want to know what kind of person you are,
even if there is no end in sight…
Chapter 10: "A New Life"
For now, at least, I’ve moved into a shelter away from the cold.
とりあえず 寒さがしのげればいいくらいで
実行した引っ越しだったが…
Isn’t this great?
いいんじゃないの？
いいんじゃないかな？ これ
This is great, isn’t it?
いやあ なんか 中々いいよね えへ…
Well, this feels quite nice.
I’ll hang a picture up for decoration or something.
絵とか飾ってみちゃったりとか
This is a lifestyle that people would admire.
憧れの生活的なものがあるよねえ
Well, even so,
まあ それでもやっぱり
it’s still under a bridge.
橋の下なんだけどね
うっうっ ひょっとして俺…
すごくバカな事をしているんじゃ…
It’s not that I don’t realize I’m doing something really stupid.
と 思わないでもない
父さんにばれたら どうなるんだろうか？
What would happen if my father found out?
Even though this is due to a debt I created,
借りを作った時点でアウトなんだが…
to actually be living under a bridge like this…
その上 こんな橋の下に住む事に
なってしまったなんて…
This isn’t good. I’m just getting more depressed.
ダメだ なんか どんどんへこんで…
Rec, can I come in?
リク 入っていいか？
You’re already in, aren’t you?
もう完璧に入ってるじゃないですか
Is that fine, or isn’t it?
いいのか？ 悪いのか？
Please enter.
どうぞー
寒いんで 早く閉めて下さい
It’s cold. Please shut the door quickly.
This is amazing.
すごいなあ
Nino-san, being Nino-san, is as vague as ever.
ニノさんはニノさんで
相変わらずいろいろ意味不明だし
What is it?
何ですか？ 何か用が…
Did you want something?
Eat this.
これ食え
Might this be a fish from the river?
これってもしかして 川の魚ですか？
Well, yeah.
当たり前だ 川以外のどこで獲れるんだ？
Where else could I have caught it?
Catching is your only concept of food.
獲る以外の発想はないんですね？
You’ve not eaten anything since yesterday, right?
お前 昨日から何も食っていないだろ？
焼いてあるから食べろ
It’s grilled, so just eat up.
Why go to all that trouble?
何でわざわざ？
Why? Well,
何でって そりゃあ
because you’re my lover.
恋人だから
I want to feed my lover when he’s hungry, at least.
恋人が腹が減ってれば
飯ぐらい食わせたくなる
Come to think of it, I’d almost forgotten that she’s my lover.
そういえば 忘れてたけど
この人 俺の恋人… 彼女なんだっけ
My girlfriend, right?
That means, in this situation,
ていう事は何だ？
あーん
I’m all alone with her in my room!
今 この状況って 彼女と部屋で
二人っきりってヤツじゃないか？
おい 食うか？
Hey, are you going to eat?
いたっ いただきますっ！
Yes, I will, thanks!
どうした？
What’s the matter?
いええっ！ 何でも！
Nothing at all!
Wh-What should I do?
ど どうしよう
So far, everything’s been so unrealistic that I’ve not thought much about it.
今までは何だか 非現実的で
何も思わなかったのに
When I look at her in such normal surroundings, Nino-san is… c-cute.
こういう日常的な物と一緒に
ニノさんを見ると…
か 可愛い…
ぺろ ぺろ ぺろ ん？
Are you eating?
食ってるか？
はい！ 食ってます！
美味しいです！ マジで はいっ！
Yes! I’m eating.
It’s delicious!
It’s seriously fine!
可愛いって事に 今更気づいたり…
I’ve only just noticed that she’s cute.
んっぐっ ぐはあっ！
大丈夫か？
Are you okay?
C-Crap, I’m so nervous.
や やばい… 緊張してきた
Even though it’s under a bridge,
I’ve never had a girl in my room.
橋の下とはいえ
女の子を部屋に入れるのは初めてだし
Wh-What should I do?
ど どうすれば…
Silence?!
無言！
I-I have to say something.
な 何か話さなきゃ… えーとー
女の子との会話 女の子との会話…
Er… Girl talk, girl talk…
ニッ ニノさんっ！
Nino-san!
あのう あ ニノさんて あああ あのぅ
Say, Nino-san! Um…
Well…
Who’s your favorite actor?
好きな芸能人は誰ですか？
どんなＣＤ聞くんですか？
What kind of CDs do you listen to?
Have you seen any movies lately?
最近何か映画見ました？
好きなブランドってあるんですか？
What brands of goods do you like?
Which beauty parlor do you go to?
美容院どこですか？
昨日ってテレビ何見ました？
What did you watch on TV yesterday?
Do you have a favorite baseball team?
好きな球団ありますか？
行きたい国はどこですか？
Which country do you want to visit?
お勧めのレストランあります？
Is there a restaurant you’d recommend?
Talk about dogs? Cats? Birds?
犬派？ 猫派？ 鳥派？
Not a single topic that could induce a response!
何一つとして
返事が返ってきそうなものは無しっ！
Nothing at all.
何でもありません
I see.
そうか
Is it possible to have normal daily conversations with Nino-san?
ニノさんと日常的な会話とか
出来るんだろうか？
What exactly is normal for Nino-san?
大体 ニノさんの日常って何だ？
All I know about Nino-san is…
ニノさんについて
俺が知っている事と言えば…
She lives under a bridge.
橋の下に住んでいる… 名前…
王様ベッドを所有
Her name.
She owns a king’s bed.
And she was born on…
そして生まれは…
Venus!
金星…
これだ
That’s it!
What is?
どれだ？
本当に金星人だなんて事あり得ない
She can’t possibly be a a Venusian.
From what I remember, Nino-san is
俺が思うに ニノさんは…
an extreme astronomy nerd and sci-fi fan.
極度の天文オタクかＳＦファンで
A nut-job who thinks she’s a Venusian.
自分は金星人 と思い込んでしまった
デンパさん
So, with that assumption and Venus as a topic, things may just get exciting.
とすれば それを前提とした金星トークで
盛り上がれるかも知れない
I’ve not seen any ghosts or aliens,
so I don’t believe in them.
俺は 宇宙人だとか幽霊だとか
そういうのは自分の目でまだ
見た事が無いから信じていない
But if that is what my savior desires, then…
だが 命の恩人がそれを望むなら…
Hey.
おい
よし… どうするか…
All right.
What should I do?
And the Jovian said,
それで 木星人のヤツが言ったんだ
“Oh? Both my hands are… the Big Bang!”
おや？僕の両手がビッグバンだぞ！ってね
Or should I go with some Venusian black humor?
金星風のブラックジョークで行くか…
We can’t keep thinking that the solar system is the center of the universe, after all.
やっぱりねえ いつまでも太陽系が
中心だと思ってちゃ ダメだと思うんだ
Should I go with Venusian politics instead?
金星風政治トークで行くか…
But they’re all so embarrassing.
どれも すごい恥ずかしいが…
おい
Hey.
Yes?!
はい？
What’s the matter?
どうした？
If you’re still hungry after the fish,
do you want to eat dragonflies?
魚足りないなら トンボ食うか？
N-No, don’t worry about me!
いっ いえ お気遣いなく
No, I mean…
ええ そうじゃなくてえ その…
Ve–
Ve?
Come on, say it!
言うんだ俺！ プライドを捨てろ！
Discard your pride!
Say it!
言え！
金星も今 春なんですかねえ？
It’s spring on Venus now, isn’t it?
Dunno.
さあ？
まあ… そうですよね
Well, that’s right.
やあぁ いい天気ですね
Such nice weather.
そうだな
Isn’t it?
Chapter 11: "Fresh Out of the Tub"
あー 風呂に入りたい
I want to take a bath…
んあ 頭かゆいし でも ここは橋の下
My scalp’s itchy, too.
But I guess I’ll have to forget bathing since I’m under a bridge.
風呂なんて
最も諦めなきゃいけないんだろうなあ
んあ はあ 銭湯も遠いしなあ
The public bath is far away, too.
Ha bi ba nono.
は ビバノンノン
Haaa bi ba nono.
ハァーア ビバノンノン
Who is that?
誰だ？
Who’s that?
誰だ？ 更に風呂に
入りたくなるような歌うたってるヤツは？
Who’s singing the song that makes me crave for a bath even more?
Bi ba no.
ビバノン
What?!
はいーっ？
Sorry, but bear with it.
悪いが我慢してくれ
村長に教わった事なんだがな
The Village Chief taught me that.
Apparently, it must be chanted during baths.
風呂に入る時には
この呪文を唱えないといけないそうだ
い… 今ここにある問題は一つ…
There’s only one question here now.
Should I look or not?
見ていいのか ダメなのか それだけだ！
That is all!
Normally, at times like this, a girl would react…
普通 こういう時の女の子の反応は…
きゃあああ！ ノビ夫さんのエッチー！
Nobio-san’s a pervert!
えっへへへへ
これだ！
Like that!
But since she didn’t react that way, doesn’t that mean it’s okay?
だが これが無いんだから
大丈夫なんじゃないか？
We’re lovers, anyway.
大体 恋人同士だし ニノさんがそういう事を
気にする人だとは思えないし
I don’t think Nino-san is the type who’d be bothered by it.
No.
いやあ！
Because Nino-san is like that,
all the more reason I shouldn’t look, right?
ニノさんがそういう人だからこそ
俺は目をつぶるべきなんじゃないか？
That’s right.
そうだ！ ニノさんに常識が無い分
俺がきっちりしないと！
I have to be sure to make up for Nino-san’s lack of common sense.
All right. Shall I get out?
よし 上がるか
N-No, you shouldn’t, Nino-san!
ダ ダメです！ ニノさん！
俺達まだ 手もつないで…
We haven’t even held hands yet!
You don’t need that kind of common sense!
そーゆー常識は いらないのにいーっ！
Chapter 12: "Sea Urchin"
Mission complete.
ミッション コンプリート
意外と鉄壁ですね
She’s surprisingly impenetrable.
And I thought you didn’t have that sort of common sense…
こーゆー常識は無い人だと思ってたのに
Well, I don’t really care, but…
いや 私は別に気にしないんだが
In the past, when I got in the usual way, the police would come.
昔 普通に入っていたら パトカーが来てな
すごく 面倒くさかったから
That was quite the bother.
Oh, that’s why you know about public indecency.
ああ だから公然わいせつ罪なんて言葉
知ってたんですね
So there are things she remembers.
一応この人も
そうやって覚えてくんだなあ…
By the way, Rec,
ところでリク お前も入ったらどうだ？
why don’t you take one?
A bath.
風呂
え？ いいんですか？
Can I?
Yeah.
ああ タオル使え 捕まるなよ
Use this towel. Don’t get busted.
いやあー いーもんだなー
This feels great.
I’ve actually yearned to try a drum bath.
実はちょっと憧れてたんだよねー
ドラム缶風呂
Really? I’m glad.
そうか 良かったな
Yeah. But once is enough, though.
ええ 一度でいいですけどね
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?
な な 何を？
すぐ終わるからよ
I’ll be done soon.
This scent…
Cleanser
この匂いは 学校の水道に置いてあった
クレンザーの匂いだ
It’s from the cleanser that’s usually used to clean school sinks.
Without a doubt, my cuticles are dying as she scratches away.
キシキシという音は 俺のキューティクルが
死んでいく音に違いない
That’s probably…
だから だろうか
That’s probably why I’m crying.
だから 泣けてくるんだろうか…
How troubling.
困った
Generally, this would be incurring a debt.
大体これは 借りになる
そう言いたいけど…
That’s what I’d like to say,
but if I spoke now, she’d hear my tearful voice.
今しゃべったら 涙声になりそうだ
あっ ていうか 湯面に映って
泣いてるのばればれだったら超恥ずかしい
That means it’d be really embarrassing if my tears were to start pattering on the water.
Nino-san.
ニノさん？
You’re playing.
遊んでますね？
I’m serious.
真剣だ
Chapter 13: "Rec-ollections"
When I was very young, my father once washed my hair.
すごく小さい時 一度だけ父さんに
頭を洗ってもらった事がある
And the day after that…
その次の日
Kou, repay all the debts you owe me.
行 今までの借りを 返しておきなさい
Now we’re even.
これで私とお前の間に 貸し借りは無しだ
From now on, please be self-sufficient.
これからは １人で生きて行きなさい
This rigid fate hit me so suddenly.
突然突きつけられた厳しい運命よりも
What’s your reply?
返事は？
Yes, sir.
はい
The lather on father’s hair washed away
with the warmth I’d felt from him the day before.
髪についた泡と一緒に
昨日の父さんの手の温かさまで
流れて行ってしまうようで
Rec, you’ll catch a cold.
リク 湯冷めするぞ
はっははは お前 頭ゴワゴワだな
Your hair’s all stiff.
あ ニノさん
Nino-san, I’ll definitely repay this de–
この借りも必ず…
私が洗いたいから 洗ったんだ
I washed it because I wanted to.
Thanks for letting me wash it.
洗わせてくれて ありがとな
Rec?
リク？
げほっ
Chapter 14: "Welcome Party"
わああー ひゅう ひゅうー
Strolling down the riverbed, I discovered many things that look like homes.
河川敷の散策をしていたら
たくさんの家らしき物を見つけた
What’s this white stuff?
何だ？ この白いの
The grass is flattened, as if it was…
草木も倒されて まるで…
Impossible.
バカな… 何を考えているんだ
宇宙人なんているわけ…
What the heck am I thinking?
No way are there aliens–
I’ve been looking for you.
探したよ
You’re the new guy, Recruit-kun, right?
新入りの リクルート君だろ？
And who might you be?!
どちら様でしょうか？
そして地球の方でしょうか？
And are you an Earthling?!
Hold the introductions for later.
自己紹介は後だ ついておいで
Come with me
to your welcoming party.
キミの歓迎会だ
やー 歓迎会だー
わああ あれみんな この河川敷の？
Those people all live on the riverbed?
Yeah, they’re all great folks.
ああ みんないい子達だよ
Let’s get along.
仲良くやって行こうじゃないか
Yeah.
He seems like a nice person.
何か いい人みたいだな
俺のオアシスになりそうな 予感
Feels like this could be my oasis.
There’s no debt in a welcoming party.
歓迎会は 借りには入らないよな？
For now, it seems we could get along well.
とりあえず 上手くやって行けそ…
All right! I’ll grill it all at once!
さあ 一気に焼くぜ！
Yay! A whole roast!
うわーい 丸焼きだ！ 男の料理だね
This is a man’s food, right?
Yeah.
おうよ
But it’s so bony that it’s difficult to eat.
でも 骨がいっぱいだから
食べる時 面倒くさいよ
Hey, hey, if you don’t eat the bones, your body will be all flabby.
おいおい　骨までしっかり食べねーと
体がふにゃふにゃになっちまうぜ
えっ そうなの？
Is that true?
Sure is.
そうだよ カルシウムを摂らなきゃ
鉄仮面がふにゃふにゃになるんだ
If you don’t get calcium, your iron mask will become brittle.
うう やだやだ そんな事になったら やだい
I don’t want that.
I don’t want that to happen.
うははは じゃあしっかり食えよ
So, eat up.
Yes!
はーい
I don’t want to get too deeply involved with them.
あの辺とは あまり深い仲になりたくないな
すごく河童と同じ匂いがする
They have the same scent as the kappa.
あ リク
Rec!
Rec.
リク
Chief, Nino-san.
村長 ニノさん
You’ve met Shiro, huh?
シロとは会えたんだな
Shiro?
シロ？
Yeah, that’s me.
ああ 俺の事だよ
No way!
そんなっ
Hahaha. Knock it off. You're stretching me out.
Naming people just to suit yourself?! That’s rude!
自分勝手な名前付けやがって
失礼だろうが！
ははは よせよ 伸びるだろ
Stop that. It’ll stretch.
Why is that guy a novice?
何であの人が シロなんだよ！
Oh, it’s because I only walk on white lines.
ああ それは
俺が白線の上しか歩かないからだよ
White lines?
白線？
Have you never played the game where you can’t step off white lines until you get home?
やんなかった？ 家に帰るまで
白線から出ちゃダメだっていうゲーム
Make
your
own
rules,
like
"if you
step off
the white
line,
girls will
hate you"
And I made a rule that I’d marry a white Cornish if I step off the white line.
俺 あれを白線から出たら
妻が白色コーニッシュになるって
ルールで始めちゃってね
I thought up a way to never walk off the white lines four years ago,
白線を引きながら歩く方法を
４年前に編み出したんだが
but I live in Hokkaido, and I’ve not been home for six years.
俺ん家 北海道だし
もう６年も帰ってないんだよ
So the white stuff I saw earlier was…
えーとー じゃあ
俺が見た さっきの白いのは…
ああ 見たんだ お恥ずかしい
That was my trail.
俺の通った跡だよ
What’s wrong?
どうした？
All right, the guest of honor is here.
よしっ 主役も来たところで
Could you introduce yourself, Rec?
自己紹介でも してもらうか
出来るな？ リク
Of course.
もちろんです
I’ll show these weirdos here that I’m clearly different from them all.
俺はここの変人どもとは違うって事を
こいつらに はっきり教えてやる！
Everyone. Pleased to meet you.
皆さん！ 初めまして
I’m the heir to and next president of the Ichinomiya Company, currently enrolled at Tokyo U, Ichinomiya Kou.
市ノ宮カンパニーの御曹司で
且つ次期社長の
Ｔ大現役合格 市ノ宮 行です！
As you all know, Ichinomiya is the world’s greatest–
皆さまご承知の通り
イチノミヤは世界的大企
くっうっ…
What the hell are you, stupid kappa?!
何すんだ この河童…
I should be asking you.
それはこっちのセリフだ
You don’t know the meaning behind changing your name, do you?
お前 名前を変えた事を
全然分かってねーだろう
Recruit. They want to hear about who you are.
What you have doesn’t matter.
リクルート
お前自身の話を聞かせて欲しいんだ
何を持ってるかは 問題じゃない
Nino-san…
ニノさん…
Our angel Nino is truly cute and lovely today, as always.
今日も 激キュート！ 激ラブリーだぜ
俺達の天使 ニノ
How true.
ホントだねー
To think that I’ve suddenly reminded these guys of their regrets…
俺はまた つい こいつらを
悔しがらせたいなんて…
Please, let me do that again.
反省します 言い直させて下さい
I’m Recruit.
俺はリクルート
I’m Nino-san’s lover.
ニノさんの恋人です
ぬおっ！
What.
おおうっ？
Chapter 15: "Battle Sister"
Why are we up so early on Sunday? Is something happening?
日曜日なのに こんな朝早くに起きて
一体何があるんですか？
It’s Mass.
ミサだ
Mass?
ミサ？
こ こんな建物が橋の下にあったなんて…
So there’s a building like that under the bridge…
It’s cool, isn’t it?
かっこいいだろう？
何年か前みんなで作ったんだ
Everyone built it a few years back, together.
Built it?
作ったって…
There are people with different occupations under this bridge.
この橋の下には
いろんな職業のヤツがいてな
The carpenter taught us a lot.
大工のヤツから いろいろ教わったんだ
色んな職業っていうと
司祭様もいらっしゃるわけで？
Different occupations…
So, there’s a priest too?
Priest?
司祭？
How to put it… The guy who conducts Mass.
なんて言うか… ミサを執り行う…
Oh, you mean Sister.
ああー シスターの事か もちろんいるぞ
Of course Sister’s here.
へー 橋の下のシスターか
Oh, a nun under the bridge, huh?
She must be as kind as the Virgin Mary.
やはり マリア様のように
優しい人なんだろうな
Perhaps this really could be my oasis.
もしかして今度こそ
本当に俺のオアシス登場か？
Look, Rec.
見ろ リク
Sister is there speaking with the Chief.
シスターならあそこだぞ
今 村長と話してる
Oh, I sense a beauty.
なんだか… 美人の予感…
Sister is giving out orders!
シスターより命ずる
Company, fall in!
全員！
整列！
Amen!
アーメン！
That’s more like a brother than a sister!
シスターっつうか ブラザー寄りだよ！
Chapter 16: "Mass"
Ni-Ni-Ni-Nino-san. Who’s that person?
ニノさん？ 何ですか？ あの人は
Shut up, Rec.
うるさいぞ リク
Th-That gun has to be fake, right? Can’t be–
ああああああの銃は偽物なんですよね？
まさか…
Be quiet. Mass has begun.
静かにしていろ ミサが始まるぞ
Fine.
よしっ 悪い事した人 お手上げ！
Those of you who’ve done bad things, raise your hands!
Aight, none!
はい 無ーし 撤収！
Disperse!
わーい
No way, seriously? Done in 5 seconds?!
嘘マジ？ ５秒で終わり？
Chapter 17: "The Gospel"
Listen up, Nino-san.
いいですか？ ニノさん
That is definitely not a Sister, and this is not Mass.
あれは絶対シスターじゃないし
これはミサじゃありません
He has dangerous-looking scars on his face, too.
何か 顔にヤバい傷もあるし
I don’t know what kind of suspicious doctrines he’ll teach.
一体どんな怪しい教えで
人を集めたのか知りませんが
His scars have nothing to do with this, right?
リク 傷は関係ないだろ
I really never learn, do I?
ホント… 学習しないな 俺は…
Sorry.
すいません
It’s fine.
いや あやまうこほはない
There’s no need to apologize.
Right! Who hasn’t got their cookie?
はーい 他にクッキーもらってない人ー
Oh, me!
あー 俺俺
Me too!
僕もー
Sister’s cookies are really yummy.
シスターのクッキー 美味しいぬー
They’re getting baited!
餌付けされとる！
Nino-san, you’re being tricked!
ニノさん 騙されてます！
You don’t have to be shy. Just go and get one.
恥ずかしがってないで
もらってくればいいだろう？
Hey.
おい
I’m not being jealous here.
羨ましいわけじゃないです
Hey, you.
お前だ
You’re Recruit, Nino’s other half, right?
貴様がリクルート　ニノの伴侶か？
Um… Is this gun real?
あの…
この銃は本物ですか？
Is your love real?
お前の愛は 本物か？
Answer me.
答えろ
If you don’t, shall I test this gun out on your head?
でなければ この銃
貴様の頭で試してやろうか？
Hey! I-I don’t know about love,
ちょっ… あ あ 愛は分かりませんが…
but my determination is real.
決心は本物です
I’ve heard the rumors.
噂には聞いている
ニノを幸せにするように
Make Nino happy.
Huh? What?
あれ… 何だ？
He’s a nice guy?
この人 いい人？
But he stinks of gunpowder.
いや でも 火薬くせーよ
I-I’ll do my best.
が 頑張ります
However, this is the first affirmation I’ve gotten for being with Nino-san.
でも ニノさんとの事 肯定的に言われたの
初めてだ
I’ll just pretend those were fireworks, then.
花火の臭いだと思って 接してみよう
So, uh, what do the rumors say?
えーと 噂って何を聞かれたんですか？
Well, rather than rumors…
いや 噂というかな…
Since you got here, more people have been coming in for confession.
貴様が来てから
懺悔室を利用する者が増えてな
To sum it up, this is what they say:
皆が口を揃えて こう言うんだ
“I want to beat up Recruit.”
リクルートをとにかく ぶん殴りたい
Everyone’s keeping their eyes on you.
皆 目が座っていたな
Oh, is that right…
あ そうですか
Recruit, I’m at the church most of the time.
リクルート 私は大体教会にいる
If anything should happen, don’t hesitate to come by.
何かあったら 遠慮せず来ていい
Well, Nino did choose you.
まあ ニノが選んだ人間だ
ここもすぐに慣れるさ
The others will get used to it.
Honestly, it doesn’t feel like I was chosen.
本当の所
選ばれたという感じは ないんだけど…
All right, Recruit.
よしっ リクルート
To those who are lost, I say unto them,
迷える貴様に 言葉を一つ くれてやろう
whosoever shall smite thee on thy right cheek,
turn to him the other also.
右の頬を殴られたら
左の頬を差し出しなさい
If you grit your teeth and get through it,
歯を食いしばっていれば…
you’ll be A-OK.
大丈ブイ
You sound sure that I’ll get beaten up!
俺が殴られる事 前提ですかー
（前提ですかー 前提ですかー 前提ですかー）
ワオーン…
I’ll be A-OK, huh?
大丈ブイか…
I’m not OK at all!
大丈夫じゃねーよっ！
Sorry, Rec, can you break a 10,000 yen note?
Yeah, are thousand notes okay?
Hey, that’s just candy, isn’t it?
No. It’s a shirikodama worth 10,000 yen.
It’s half-eaten, too!
Next time: 3 Bridge.
あの日夕暮れ
It’s so sticky.
Notes: (14:51) Shiro can, among other things, mean novice or white.
(23:37) A shirikodama is a mythical ball in one’s anus that kappa seek.
Illustration: Hiroyuki
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
もう行かなくちゃ
この空泣き出す前に
サカサマになって
君の事探して
いつまでも僕らは
たどり着けないまま
橋の下に立って
流れる渦に在って
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
悪りぃリク １万円崩してくんね？
はい 1000円でいいですか？
って それ飴玉じゃないですか
ちげーよ １万円相当の尻子玉だよ
しかも 食べかけだ！
次回 「３ ＢＲＩＤＧＥ」
べったべただ